[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：成员来自反应侧的发泄朋友。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Member are from a vent friend from the reactive side.
下面是我们如何设置一个监听佛法通风口的事件。
Here's how we could set up an event that listens for Dhamma vents.
我的意思是一个倾听支配地位的频道。
I mean a channel that listens for dominance.
我在第二行建立了一个通道，我给它附加了一个点击处理程序，然后
I set up a channel on line two I attach a click handler to it and
您注意到第4行，我调用PUT Async。
you notice on line 4, I call put Async.
为什么我不调用PUT？
Why am I not calling put?
嗯，因为我现在不在发电机里。
Well, cuz I'm not inside of a generator right now.
我在单击处理程序中，这是一个普通的普通函数。
I'm inside of a click handler, which is a plain old normal function.
如果我想听，putAsync会给我一个承诺
That putAsync would return me a Promise if I wanted to listen to be
告诉我卖出已经完成了。
told that the put had completed.
但也许我不在乎它是否完成。
But maybe I don't care whether it completes.
我只是将事件对象放入通道。
I'm just gonna put the event object into the channel.
然后有一个真正的合法的围棋程序等待听到
And then there is a real legitimate go routine that's waiting to hear for
12号线上的信息，他试图从那个频道获取。
that message on line 12 he's trying to take from that channel.
所以他只是在一个真正的循环中旋转，每次你点击它或
So he just spinning in a while true loop and each time you click that or
每次你做那件事。
each time you do that event.
我要去，我要得到通知，因为我能够
I'm going to take I'm going to get notified by that by being able to take
我要把它打印出来。
from the channel and I'm gonna print it out.
所以我在做什么事，小老鼠。
So what event am I doing, mousemove.
但这意味着每次当我移动光标时，mousemove事件都会触发
But what this means is every time the mousemove event fires as I move my cursor
在这个元素的周围，我将通过通道发送一条消息
around on this element, I'm gonna send a message down the channel that's
事件对象并打印出控制台中的x，y位置。
the event object and print out the x, y location in the console.
所以我们要通过激发我们的事件来适应用户界面元素
So we gonna adapt to user interface elements by having our events fire and
把事情往下推。
pushing things down a channel.
第4行看起来与我们对Observables所做的非常相似吗？
Does line 4 look an awful lot like what we did with observables?
我们有一条小溪，我们将事件推入一条小溪
We had a stream and we were pushing events into a stream and
另一个人正在把这些事件从流水中拿走，并观察它们。
somebody else was taking the events off the stream and observing them.
是非常相似的概念。
Is very similar concepts here.
我们在这里建模的主要区别是
The major difference between what we're modeling here and
我们用可观察到的主要差异建模的是背压，因为我们
what we model with observables major difference is back pressure, cuz we
我可以模型，我不希望你给我任何其他东西，直到我准备好接受它。
can model that I don't want you to send me anything else until I'm ready to take it.
那是免费的。
That comes for free.
我们不需要做任何额外的工作。
We don't have to do any extra work.
我们不需要将我们的可观察到的从热转换为冷来表示这一点，或者
We don't have to convert our observable from hot to cold to signal that, or
任何像那样疯狂的事情。
anything crazy like that.
我们只是不从频道里拿，那就是
We just don't take from the channel and that's
自动内置背压。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：SO
an automatic built in back pressure. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
当你做的时候，你会得到最近的鼠标事件吗？
when you do take would you get the most recent mouse event?
或者你会得到它？&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，在这种情况下？
Or would you get it? &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, in this case?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：每次活动
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Every time the event
大火，我们要往溪流里放点东西。
fires, we're going to be putting something into the stream.
所以你会以同样快的速度，他们可能会更快地堆积起来。
So you'd be taking them as fast, and they could be piling up faster.
但是您注意到我们这里没有任何超时，所以我们将把它们当作
But you notice we don't have any timeouts here, so we're going to take them as
尽可能快。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：SO
fast as we possibly can. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
放置putAsync然后覆盖前一个，
putting putAsync then overriding the previous one,
是这个想法吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不是。
is that the idea? &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: No.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：如果您不匹配每个
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you're not matching every
单人，对吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以每次
single one, right? &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So every time it's going
试着放到频道上，它会说我还不能放到频道上
to try to put onto the channel, it's going to say I can't put onto the channel yet
因为有人还没准备好接受。
because somebody is not ready to take it yet.
所以我会，假设发生了一堆鼠标移动，
So I'm going to have, let's say a bunch of mouse moves happened,
100次鼠标移动会发生，但围棋例程从未触发过一次抓取。
a 100 mouse moves happen, but the go routine had never fired a take yet.
我有100个单独的等待承诺
I have 100 separate waiting Promises that were all
为了试图推动他们的活动顺流而下，但是
in order going to try to push their event down the stream but
直到第一次拍摄发生之前，这些事件都没有被放入流中。
none of those events had been put on the stream yet until the first take happens.
所以如果我移动鼠标真的很快，然后这个围棋例程就会发生。
So if I move my mouse real fast and then this go routine happen.
他会把所有这些事件都打印出来，全部100个都打印出来。
He would get all of those events and print out all 100 of them.
这不是丢弃任何事件。
That's not throwing any events away.
重要的是要注意，这里的一些内容没有映射
It's important to note that some of the things here don't map
完全可以观察到，例如丢弃我们不关心的消息
perfectly to observable so for example throwing away messages that we don't care
关于你必须使用像alts这样的东西。
about you're going have to use something like alts.
如果你想要有你不能拥有的频道的概念
If you want this notion of being able to have channels that you're not
你正在发送的东西，没有人在另一端听。
that you're sending stuff down that nobody is on the other end listening to.
您可以使通道具有缓冲模式，因此
You can make channels into having a buffering mode so
通道可以具有多于缓冲区大小1的缓冲区。
channels can have more than buffer size one.
所以你可以让它们缓冲
So you could make them buffered and
说我想在开始听之前花十个这样的时间。
say I want to take ten of that sort of time before I start listening.
很多变化。
Lots of variations.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：只是非常快，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Just real quickly,
给你看看，CSP。
just show you, CSP.
我再次将相同的机制移植到异步中，所以
I ported the same mechanism into asynquence, again, so
你不必去学习其他图书馆。
you don't have to go learn some other library.
您可以使用相同的库完成所有这些操作。
You can do it all with the same library.
你把围棋程序放到Runner里。
You put go routines into runner.
你就是这么做的。
That's how you do it.
所以我有ASQ。，基本上是ASQ。
So I have ASQ., basically ASQ.
在你已经看到的每一个东西面前。
In front of every one of those things that you've already seen.
它与库中的API完全相同，但名称空间具有ASQ。
It's the exact same APIs that are in the library but the namespace has ASQ.
当着他们所有人的面。
in front of all of them.
否则，这是完全相同的概念。
Otherwise, it's exactly the same concept.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我几乎跳过了一个重要的细节。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I almost skipped over an important detail.
还记得你之前问过关于全局变量的问题吗？
Remember you were asking earlier about global variables.
我不喜欢有全局变量的概念。
I don't like the notion of having global variables.
所以我自动为每个围棋程序创建了一个频道。
So I automatically created a channel for each go routine.
他们都可以参考创建的一个通道。
There is one channel created that they all get reference to.
因此它们自动至少有一个可以在其上进行通信的通道。
So they automatically have at least one channel that they can all communicate on.
如果你想制作更多的频道，你可以制作频道
And if you wanna make more channels you can make channels and
让他们通过频道。
send them over the channel.
所以你根本不需要使用任何全局变量。
So you don't have to use any global variables at all.
这是我的实现与其他实现的一个不同之处。
That's one difference with my implementation versus the others.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：以防万一，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: In case,
此ch是免费创建的或-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它是创建的
this ch is created for free or- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's created
由异步用户自动完成。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：不是在其他地方创建的？
automatically by async ones. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Not created somewhere else?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不，它是创建的，传入的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: No it's created passed in
为了你。
for you.
因为假设每个人都需要至少一个通道
Because the assumption is every body is gonna need at least one channel so
让我们去创造想给你它，而不是让你自己。
let's go and create want to give it to you, instead of making you make your own.